Hey, how are you, I'm Eddie.
Hi, I'm Jessica.
Nice to meet you.
How are you?
So Trump is defying the first, fourth, fifth.
Fifth and 14th, and maybe the 22nd soon.
Okay, so I wanna focus on the first and the fifth.
Okay.
So you say that Trump is defying the First Amendment.
Can you give me an example?
For example, he banned the Associated Press
from attending White House events.
A Trump-appointed judge said
that was against the First Amendment.
He's been cracking down on media organizations
he doesn't like over their speech.
If they say stuff he doesn't like,
he, for example, he called-
Cracking down how?
So for example, he banned the Associated Press
from attending White House events
because they said-
I can't go to the White House either.
It's the Gulf of Mexico.
That's not how it works.
They were already at the White House.
He deprived them for access,
so he punished them for their speech.
But are they allowed to go to the press?
Which is why a judge he appointed,
Trevor McFadden, said this was contrary
to the First Amendment.
A Trump-appointed judge.
He's called MSNBC and CNN illegal.
Media organizations are not ipso facto illegal.
But that's free speech.
He can call them whatever they want.
Attacking the media?
Yeah, he can attack them.
As the executive?
Yeah, he can say whatever he wants.
That's literally the First Amendment.
He can say whatever he wants.
Absolutely.
But the media can't say what they want.
They do.
But he's going after them.
He's suing them.
He's using lawsuits to crack down on the press.
They used lawsuits to give him 34 felonies
that Hillary Clinton did.
No media gave him a lawsuit.
No, but people on the Democratic side.
We're not talking about the Democrats.
Okay.